a-pdf.com 2017-12-11

# Privacy Policy [A-PDF.com]

A-PDF.com collects name, IP address and other information (such as e-mail address) on some parts on the website and registration service providers. This is done to help us provide our customers with the best customer service and with valuable information regarding relevant products and services from A-PDF.com. 

A-PDF.com is dedicated to protecting personal information and will make every reasonable effort to handle collected information appropriately. All information collected, as well as related requests, will be handled as carefully and efficiently as possible in accordance with our standards for integrity and objectivity. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.  

## Personal Information 

No personal information is collected by A-PDF.com from visitors to our website, when viewing pages, or when downloading software from our website. We also do not collect or harvest the EMail addresses of people who EMail us directly. We only use them to respond to your queries. We do use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. But IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

## Newsletter

If you subscribed our A-PDF Newsletter (it will be used to inform you of our products news and promotion only), your information will **not** be sold, rented or leased to a third-party, and you can remove your name and email from the list at any time.

## Order

Here a user must provide contact information (such as name and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customers' orders. Some of this information is provided to A-PDF.com (such as name and address, and e-mail address, but not credit card numbers) and is used for order fulfillment. When placing an order, you should be aware that the order is placed with a third party distributor, on their web site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
